	questionList = questionList.concat([
	
	//Imperative   4
	{question:"Don't eat the apples.", answers:["No coma las manzanas.","No comas las manzanas.","No coman las manzanas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No coma las manzanas.", answers:["Don't eat the apples.","Do not eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No comas las manzanas.", answers:["Don't eat the apples.","Do not eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No coman las manzanas.", answers:["Don't eat the apples.","Do not eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not eat the apples.", answers:["No comamos las manzanas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No comamos las manzanas.", answers:["Let's not eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eat the apples.", answers:["Coma las manzanas.","Come las manzanas.","Coman las manzanas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Coma las manzanas.", answers:["Eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Come las manzanas.", answers:["Eat the apples.","He eats the apples.","She eats the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Coman las manzanas.", answers:["Eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's eat the apples.", answers:["Comamos las manzanas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Comamos las manzanas.", answers:["Let's eat the apples."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No seas un extraño.", answers:["Don't be a stranger."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No sea un extraño.", answers:["Don't be a stranger."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No sean extraños.", answers:["Don't be strangers."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Don't be a stranger.", answers:["No seas un extraño.","No sea un extraño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Don't be strangers.", answers:["No sean extraños."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No seamos extraños.", answers:["Let's not be strangers."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not be strangers.", answers:["No seamos extraños."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sé un héroe.", answers:["Be a hero."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Sea un héroe.", answers:["Be a hero."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Sean héroes.", answers:["Be heroes."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Be a hero.", answers:["Sé un héroe.","Sea un héroe."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Be heroes.", answers:["Sean héroes."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Seamos héroes.", answers:["Let's be heroes."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's be heroes.", answers:["Seamos héroes."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Don't drink the water.", answers:["No beba el agua.","No bebas el agua.","No beban el agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No beba el agua.", answers:["Don't drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No bebas el agua.", answers:["Don't drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No beban el agua.", answers:["Don't drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not drink the water.", answers:["No bebamos el agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No bebamos el agua.", answers:["Let's not drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Drink the water.", answers:["Beba el agua.","Bebe el agua.","Beban el agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Beba el agua.", answers:["Drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Bebe el agua.", answers:["Drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Beban el agua.", answers:["Drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's drink the water.", answers:["Bebamos el agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Bebamos el agua.", answers:["Let's drink the water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Don't write letters.", answers:["No escriba cartas.","No escribas cartas.","No escriban cartas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No escriba cartas.", answers:["Don't write letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No escribas cartas.", answers:["Don't write letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No escriban cartas.", answers:["Don't write letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not write letters.", answers:["No escribamos cartas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No escribamos cartas.", answers:["Let's not write letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Write some letters.", answers:["Escriba unas cartas.","Escribe unas cartas.","Escriban unas cartas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Escriba unas cartas.", answers:["Write some letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Escribe unas cartas.", answers:["Write some letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Escriban unas cartas.", answers:["Write some letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's write some letters.", answers:["Escribamos unas cartas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ecribamos unas cartas.", answers:["Let's write some letters."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Don't read the book.", answers:["No lea el libro.","No leas el libro.","No lean el libro."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No lea el libro.", answers:["Don't read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No leas el libro.", answers:["Don't read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No lean el libro.", answers:["Don't read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not read the book.", answers:["No leamos el libro."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No leamos el libro.", answers:["Let's not read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Read the book.", answers:["Lea el libro.","Lee el libro.","Lean el libro."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Lea el libro.", answers:["Read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Lee el libro.", answers:["Read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Lean el libro.", answers:["Read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's read the book.", answers:["Leamos el libro."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Leamos el libro.", answers:["Let's read the book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Don't cook fish.", answers:["No cocine pescado.","No cocines pescado.","No cocinen pescado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocine pescado.", answers:["Don't cook fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No cocines pescado.", answers:["Don't cook fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"No cocinen pescado.", answers:["Don't cook fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's not cook fish.", answers:["No cocinemos pescado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocinemos pescado.", answers:["Let's not cook fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Cook the fish.", answers:["Cocine el pescado.","Cocina el pescado.","Cocinen el pescado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Cocine el pescado.", answers:["Cook the fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Cocina el pescado.", answers:["Cook the fish.","He cooks the fish.","She cooks the fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Cocinen el pescado.", answers:["Cook the fish."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Let's cook the fish.", answers:["Cocinemos el pescado."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Cocinemos el pescado.", answers:["Let's cook the fish."], language:"English"}
	
	
	]);
